

BOLDIZSÁR NAGY

STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

Multi-lingual student with both physical and office work experience. I consider myself a great team worker and I can easily establish friendships. My main goal is to get national and international connections while studying abroad and deepening my knowledge in computer science.

EDUCATION

University of Groningen COMPUTING SCIENCE

FACULTY OF SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING 2021-

Kölcsey Ferenc Gimnázium Budapest

FRENCH-HUNGARIAN BILINGUAL HIGHSCHOOL, 2015-2020

Advanced Final Exam in Informatics, English and French language

Intermediate Exam in History, Hungarian grammar and literature, mathematics

Fabriczius József Primary School, Veresegyház

ELEMENTARY SCHOOL 2007-2015

UNIVERSITY INTERNSHIP

Currently enrolling to a course where we participate in a group internship with the university to develop a module for a client in the software that they use.

INFORMATION

Date of birth: 03 June 2000 Nationality: hungarian

Cell: +36 20 402 0477 / +31 6 21 91 64 51

Email: nagyboldi2000@gmail.com

Address: 9742 SJ Grote Beerstraat 206-k22

Groningen, Netherlands

SKILLS

-Intermediate knowledge of Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Access)

-Basic knowledge of programming languages (SQL, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

- Lower Intermediate knowledge of programming languages (C++, Haskell, C, Powershell)

-Upper Intermediate knowledge of programming languages(C#, Swift, Java)

- Basic Adobe Photoshop knowledge

- Version Control (Git)

- OMPT-D Mathematics Exam 95%

-Domain hosting.

HOBBIES

-Sports (such as calisthenics, football, handball, basketball, table tennis, lacrosse)

- -Reading, movies.
- -Playing the piano
- -Programming: Fun console projects (mostly C#), IOS development with SwiftUI.

LANGUAGES

Hungarian - native language

English - B2 TELC Intermiate english exam English - IELTS Academic exam (7.5) C1

French - C1 Advanced

EXPERIENCE

System Administrator Intern

MEDICAL SERVICE OF ZUGLÓ 06/2020 - 08/2020 BUDAPEST

The biggest public health institution in Budapest's 14th district.

Tasks

- Configuring the clinic's computers for usage
- Providing technical support for the healthcare professionals of the institution
- Creating a database of all the technological equipment in use at the time of my employment **Thuisbezorgd driver**

THUISBEZORGD GRONINGEN 09/2021 - 11/2022 Food courier as a bicycle driver.

EXPERIENCE

Full-stack web developer

SMEEDIJZER INTERNET IN GRONINGEN 12/2021 – PRESENT Small company that specialised in creating Wordpress websites for clients.

Tasks:

- -Creating and designing template Wordpress websites from scratch.
- -Fixing bugs/adding new pages and content to existing custom Wordpress websites.
- -Editing assets needed for the clients (Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator)
- -Responsibility for domain hosting: Purchase URL's, configuring DNS records.
- -Communication with clients to satisfy their needs.